[{"Id":"0be3368a-247e-4174-9266-aa61f096e9a1","Question":"\u042F\u043A\u0435 \u0440\u0456\u0432\u043D\u044F\u043D\u043D\u044F \u043E\u043F\u0438\u0441\u0443\u0454 \u043A\u043E\u043B\u043E \u0437 \u0446\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0440\u043E\u043C \u0443 \u043F\u043E\u0447\u0430\u0442\u043A\u0443 \u043A\u043E\u043E\u0440\u0434\u0438\u043D\u0430\u0442 \u0456 \u0440\u0430\u0434\u0456\u0443\u0441\u043E\u043C 5?","Type":"radio","Options":["x^2 \u002B y^2 = 25","x^2 - y^2 = 25","x \u002B y = 1","x^2 \u002B y^2 = 3"],"CorrectIndexes":[0],"CorrectAnswerText":""},{"Id":"dda65d66-a736-4b2a-9550-de8b9e83268a","Question":"\u042F\u043A\u0430 \u0434\u043E\u0432\u0436\u0438\u043D\u0430 \u0432\u0435\u043A\u0442\u043E\u0440\u0430 (3, 4)?","Type":"radio","Options":["5","7","3","6"],"CorrectIndexes":[0],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"545a3795-15f0-4781-8e80-40f17e29e9d7","Question":"\u041F\u0440\u044F\u043C\u0456 \u043D\u0430\u0437\u0438\u0432\u0430\u044E\u0442\u044C\u0441\u044F \u043F\u0435\u0440\u043F\u0435\u043D\u0434\u0438\u043A\u0443\u043B\u044F\u0440\u043D\u0438\u043C\u0438, \u044F\u043A\u0449\u043E \u043A\u0443\u0442 \u043C\u0456\u0436 \u043D\u0438\u043C\u0438:","Type":"radio","Options":["60\u00B0","45\u00B0","90\u00B0","180\u00B0"],"CorrectIndexes":[2],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"5aae17aa-dcef-456c-8ddf-cf551331ba7d","Question":"\u0421\u043A\u0456\u043B\u044C\u043A\u0438 \u043A\u043E\u043E\u0440\u0434\u0438\u043D\u0430\u0442 \u043C\u0430\u0454 \u0442\u043E\u0447\u043A\u0430 \u0432 \u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0438\u043C\u0456\u0440\u043D\u043E\u043C\u0443 \u043F\u0440\u043E\u0441\u0442\u043E\u0440\u0456?","Type":"radio","Options":["2","3","4","1"],"CorrectIndexes":[1],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"20aeedb3-dfc3-413b-84d4-c50b664dea2c","Question":"\u041E\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0456\u0442\u044C \u0432\u0441\u0456 \u0432\u0435\u043A\u0442\u043E\u0440\u0438, \u043F\u0435\u0440\u043F\u0435\u043D\u0434\u0438\u043A\u0443\u043B\u044F\u0440\u043D\u0456 \u0434\u043E (1, 0):","Type":"checkbox","Options":["(0, 1)","(1, 1)","(0, -1)","(1, 0)"],"CorrectIndexes":[0,2],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"4b07b11c-8fa3-4031-95ec-6ad3e8c8e2e3","Question":"\u042F\u043A\u0456 \u0437 \u043D\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043D\u0438\u0445 \u0442\u043E\u0447\u043E\u043A \u043B\u0435\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044C \u043D\u0430 \u043E\u0441\u0456 X?","Type":"checkbox","Options":["(3, 0)","(0, 2)","(-4, 0)","(1, 1)"],"CorrectIndexes":[0,2],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"3b2833fd-f2ee-4c28-8e46-e0b113aa9165","Question":"\u041E\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0456\u0442\u044C \u0432\u0441\u0456 \u043F\u0430\u0440\u0438 \u043F\u0430\u0440\u0430\u043B\u0435\u043B\u044C\u043D\u0438\u0445 \u0432\u0435\u043A\u0442\u043E\u0440\u0456\u0432:","Type":"checkbox","Options":["(2,4) \u0456 (1,2)","(1,0) \u0456 (0,1)","(-3,-6) \u0456 (0,2)","(-3,-6) \u0456 (1,2)"],"CorrectIndexes":[0],"CorrectAnswerText":null},{"Id":"6ea40677-9bc3-4a06-a506-5781592c9d1b","Question":"\u0421\u043A\u0456\u043B\u044C\u043A\u0438 \u0433\u0440\u0430\u0434\u0443\u0441\u0456\u0432 \u043C\u0430\u0454 \u043F\u0440\u044F\u043C\u0438\u0439 \u043A\u0443\u0442?","Type":"text","Options":[],"CorrectIndexes":[],"CorrectAnswerText":"90"},{"Id":"a40b4cfc-f7a2-4f9d-ae7c-29f8ffd30600","Question":"\u042F\u043A\u0430 \u043A\u043E\u043E\u0440\u0434\u0438\u043D\u0430\u0442\u0430 Y \u0443 \u0442\u043E\u0447\u043A\u0438 (5, -3)?","Type":"text","Options":[],"CorrectIndexes":[],"CorrectAnswerText":"-3"},{"Id":"92483535-d8b4-4616-b118-b144a9765ec0","Question":"\u041D\u0430\u043F\u0438\u0448\u0456\u0442\u044C \u0440\u0456\u0432\u043D\u044F\u043D\u043D\u044F \u043F\u0440\u044F\u043C\u043E\u0457 \u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0437 \u043F\u043E\u0447\u0430\u0442\u043E\u043A \u043A\u043E\u043E\u0440\u0434\u0438\u043D\u0430\u0442 \u0437 \u043A\u0443\u0442\u043E\u0432\u0438\u043C \u043A\u043E\u0435\u0444\u0456\u0446\u0456\u0454\u043D\u0442\u043E\u043C 2","Type":"text","Options":[],"CorrectIndexes":[],"CorrectAnswerText":"y=2x"}]